# Isidro Servin

# FullStack Software Engineer

- ism210296@gmail.com
- +1-236-514-0350
- linkedin.com/in/isidro-servín-5797a2176

#### About me

Highly motivated and experienced full-stack web developer with 4 years of experience in developing, maintaining, and updating web applications. Strong skills in front-end development using ReactJS and VueJS frameworks, and back-end development with Express/NodeJS and Django/Python. Proficient in modern web development technologies such as JavaScript, CSS, jQuery, HTML5, and Bootstrap. Familiar with database management in SQL Server, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB.

## Work Experience



### **Software Engineer.**

Think Future Technologies.

May 2023 - Present (9 months).

TFT supplements its services with self-developed libraries/solutions/frameworks in the areas of Software Development, Testing, DevOps, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Blockchain and IoT.

#### Activities:

- Development of clean, testable and maintainable code in languages such as JavaScript, NodeJS, ReactJS, TypeScript, VueJS, Python.
- Together with my team, we have developed, maintained, and tested several web applications for clients.
- I collaborated in the backend creation of an application for a school using Nodejs with Express and TypeScript as development tools.



#### Full-Stack Web Developer.

Apocalipsis Automation.

January 2020 - May 2023(3 years, 4 months).

Apocalipsis Automation is a company dedicated to providing a wide expert response to any industrial need in the area of automation and control.

#### Activities:

- Developed and maintained web applications for the company's clients in the automation and control industry.
- Utilized VueJS and ReactJS frameworks for front-end development and Express/NodeJS for back-end development.
- Implemented modern web development technologies such as JavaScript, CSS, JQuery, HTML5, Bootstrap, Graphql, Axios and Jest.
- Improved web application performance by optimizing code and implementing best practices.



## Web Developer

Legalex GS.

April 2021 - December 2021 (8 months).

Legalex is a Certification Services Provider (PSC) accredited by the Ministry of Economy to provide the services of Issuance of Certificates of Conservation of Data Messages in accordance with NOM-151-SCFI-2016 and Digital Time Stamps (Timestamp).

Performed activities:

- Developed, maintained and updated existing components in commercial products.
- Utilized Java, JS, CSS, JQuery, Java Servlets, JSP, HTML5, AJAX for back-end and front-end web development.
- Implemented PostgreSQL v13 as the database management system.
- Utilized Bitbucket for version control.



# Web and Android Developer (Internship) Ecovive.

June 2019 - December 2019 (6 months)

- Developed a web application to control the inventory of the construction company using CodeIgniter framework, Bootstrap v4 and GoogleCharts.
- Developed an Android application similar to UberEats that allowed the company's restaurant to make home deliveries, using Android Studio, Kotlin and FireBase as a NoSQL real-time database.

## **Education History**



Software Development Diploma Institution: Red Deer Polytechnic. Year of Graduation: March 2024



Bachelor's Degree in Computer Systems Engineering.

Institution: Technological Institute of Morelia.

Year of Graduation: 2019

# Languajes

- SpanishEnglish
- French
- Portuguese
- 70 % 50 %

100 %

80 %

# Git Repository



https://github.com/isidroServin

## Relevant Skills

- Front-end Development:
  ReactJS, VueJS, JavaScript,
  CSS, JQuery, HTML5,
  Bootstrap, ApexCharts, Jest,
  TypeScript.
- Back-end Development: Express/NodeJS, Java, Java Servlets, JSP.
- Database Management: SQLServer, mongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL
- Version Control: GIT, Bitbucket.
- Containerization: Docker.
- AWS.